

# MARCIN KURTZ

+48 662 466 302

kurtz.marcin@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/marcin-kurtz/github.com/mkIO

### BIO

Senior Fullstack Engineer and Lead Developer with over 8 years' experience in delivering modern web applications utilizing multiple frameworks (React, Angular) with the latest .NET framework, together with implementing DevOps solutions targeting Azure Cloud and on-premise solutions.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor of Engineering | Informatics2011 – 2015Faculty of Applied Mathematics, Silesian University of TechnologyGliwice, PolandMaster of Engineering | Applied Mathematics and Cryptography2007 – 2014Faculty of Applied Mathematics, Silesian University of TechnologyGliwice, Poland

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Lead Developer 01/2021 - present

Future Processing Sp. z o.o.

Gliwice, Poland

- **Responsibilites**: Designing the architecture of software products and APIs, software development, implementing devops infrastructure, bug fixing and refactoring, developing new business critical features, core review
- **Technologies**: : C#, TypeScript, Powershell, .NET Core/5/6, React, REST API Services, Azure Cloud Services/Functions, Azure SDK, Azure SQL Server, Azure Service Bus, Terraform

# **Senior Software Developer**

07/2018 - 01/2021

Future Processing Sp. z o.o.

Gliwice, Poland

- **Responsibilites**: Designing the architecture of software products and APIs, software development, bug fixing and refactoring, developing new business critical features, code review
- **Technologies**: .NET Core, Angular, Powershell, REST API Services, Azure Services, Azure DevOps and Octopus Deployment pipelines, C#, TypeScript, Azure SQL Server, Azure Service Bus, OData Services

#### **Medium Software Developer**

07/2014 - 07/2018

Future Processing Sp. z o.o.

Gliwice, Poland

- **Responsibilites**: Application development, bug fixing, developing new business critical features, refactoring, code review, implementing backend services
- Technologies: ASP.NET, NET 4.7, WCF, XSLT with XML, SQL Server, VB.NET, C#, Chef

# Junior Software Developer

07/2013 - 06/2014

Future Processing Sp. z o.o.

Gliwice, Poland

- Application development
- Technologies: ASP.NET, NET 4, WCF, SQL Server, XML with XML, VB.NET, C#, JavaScript

# CERTIFICATES

AZ-204: Developing Solutions for Microsoft Azure	01/2022
Developing Solutions for Microsoft Azure	
<b>70-486: Developing ASP .NET 4.5 MVC Web Applications</b> Developing ASP .NET 4.5 MVC Web Applications	12/2015
<b>70-480: Programming in HTML 5 with JavaScript and CSS3</b> HTML 5 with JavaScript and CSS3	07/2015
M101N: MongoDB for .NET Developers  Developing MongoDB solutions for .NET applications	06/2015

# Languages

Polish (native), English (B1), French (A1)

# **Document Creation**

Microsoft Office Suite, LaTex, Markdown

# Web technologies

ASP.NET, .NET, HTML5, CSS, SASS, Less, JavaScript, Typescript, React, Angular, Kendo UI, REST API, ASP Core Web API, .NET Minimal API, ASP Core MVC, Razor, Razor Pages, Singnal R, OAuth, Open Connect, Azure AD, Azure B2C, Auth0, One Login, RxJS, Entity Framework, NoSQL databases

## Cloud

Azure Services, Azure CLI, Azure RM, Cognitive Services, Service Bus, Serverless, Azure SQL, Cosmos DB, Azure Front Door, VNET and security, Chef, Terraform.

#### Mobile

Xamarin, .NET Maui

# Languages

C#, TypeScript, Javascript, Powershell.

#### **Tools**

Visual Studio, ReSharper, VS Code, Rider, Docker, Git, Azure DevOps, GitHub, RabbitMQ.

#### Architecture

Designing solution architecture, on premise/cloud based.

Supporting client with architecture decisions, mentoring with proper implementation.

#### **Practices**

Domain Driven Design, CQS, CQRS, TDD, Aspect Oriented programing, reactive programing, functional programing.